import {Quizmodel} from "../models/index"


export const MathQuestions:Quizmodel[] = [
    {
    prompt:"121 Divided by 11 is",
    options:["11", "10","19","18"],
    answer:"11"
},

{
    prompt:"60 Times of 8 Equals to",
    options:["480","300","250","400"],
    answer:"480"
},

{
    prompt:"What is the next prime number after 7?",
    options:["13","12","14","11"],
    answer:"11"
},
{
    prompt:"What is 6% Equals to?",
    options:["0.06","0.6","00.006","0.00006"],
    answer:"0.06"
}
,{
    prompt:"How many years are there in a deacade?",
    options:["13","12","10","11"],
    answer:"10"
}

]

export const EnglishQuestions:Quizmodel[]=[
    {
    prompt:"Identify the Noun, I live in Amsterdam",
    options:["In","Live","Amsterdam", "I"],
    answer:"Amsterdam"
},
{
    prompt:"Identify the Noun, I visited the Eiffel Tower in Paris",
    options:["The","Paris","Eiffel Tower and Paris","Eiffel Tower"],
    answer:"Eiffel Tower nad Paris"
},
{
    prompt:" Identify the Noun, Bhutan is a beautiful country",
    options:["A","Country","Beautiful","Bhutan"],
    answer:"Bhutan"
},
{
    prompt:" Identify the Noun, Summer is very hot",
    options:["Summer","very","Hot","is"],
    answer:"Summer"
},
{
    prompt:" Identify the Noun, The moon looks so beautiful",
    options:["Looks","Moon","The","Beautiful"],
    answer:"Moon"
}
]

export const ScienceQuestions:Quizmodel[]=[
    {
    prompt:"What does DNA stand for?",
    options:["Dexy Nuclei Acid", "Dextrosenuclei acid", "Deoxyribonucleic acid","Deltanuclei acid"],
    answer:"Deoxyribonucleic acid"
},
{
    prompt:"How many bones does a human",
    options:["206","500","350","400"],
    answer:"206"
}
,
{
    prompt:"What is the study of mushrooms ?",
    options:["Biology","Microbiology","Mycology","Pathology"],
    answer:"Mycology"
}
,
{
    prompt:"Hardest substance on earth",
    options:["Sliver","Diamond","Rocks","Iron"],
    answer:"Diamond"
},
{
    prompt:"Concepts of gravity was brought about by?",
    options:["Faraday","Newton","Geuss","Patrick"],
    answer:"Newton"
}
]

export const generalQuestions:Quizmodel[]=[
    {
        prompt:"Where was 2022 world cup hosted",
        options:["Canada","South Africa","Quatar","USA"],
        answer:"Quatar"
    },
    {
        prompt:"BBC stands for?",
        options:["British Broadcasting Corporation","Britain Broadcasting Corps","Banglore Casting Coporate","British Broadcasting Corps"],
        answer:"British Broadcasting Corporation"
    },
    {
        prompt:"How many wives did Henry marry",
        options:["Six","One","Two","Three"],
        answer:"Six"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt:"How many makes up a dozen?",
        options:["12","10","8","15"],
        answer:"12"
    }
    ,
    {
        prompt:"Which country won Quatar 2022 world cup",
        options:["Nigeria","Brazil","Portugal","Argentina"],
        answer:"Argentina"
    }

]